[
  {
    "id": "557",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which captures a wide variety of metrics?",
      "answers": [
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudTrail",
        "stderr",
        "stdout"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudWatch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "558",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which captures endpoint invocation, endpoint instance, training, transformation and Ground Truth metrics available in addition to algorithmic-specific metrics?",
      "answers": [
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudTrail",
        "stderr",
        "stdout"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudWatch"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "559",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With CloudWatch most SageMaker-specific metrics are available at ______ frequency for quick reactions",
      "answers": [
        "1-minute",
        "5-minute",
        "10-minute",
        "1-hour"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["1-minute"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "560",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With CloudWatch statistics are kept for ______ to provide plenty of historical information on model performance and trends",
      "answers": [
        "15 months",
        "15 minutes",
        "1 month",
        "5 months"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["15 months"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "561",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With CloudWatch metrics have a ______ on the console",
      "answers": [
        "2 week limit",
        "1 week limit",
        "2 day limit",
        "1 day limit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["2 week limit"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "562",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With CloudWatch metrics are collected and sent every ______ for training and prediction jobs on the console",
      "answers": [
        "5 minutes",
        "1 minute",
        "2 minutes",
        "10 minutes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["5 minutes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "563",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Any stdout or stderr messages from ______, ______, or ______ is sent to CloudWatch logs (Select 3)",
      "answers": [
        "notebook instances",
        "algorithm containers",
        "model containers",
        "inference containers"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["notebook instances",
        "algorithm containers",
        "model containers"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "564",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Captures any API calls made by or on behalf of SageMaker within your account",
      "answers": [
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudTrail",
        "S3",
        "stdout"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudTrail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "565",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "By default, the last ______ of events are visible in CloudTrail Event History",
      "answers": [
        "90 days",
        "30 days",
        "10 days",
        "20 days"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["90 days"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "566",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can set up a CloudTrail to store logs on ______ to reference for as long as you would like, as well as practice lifecycle processes like archive to ______",
      "answers": [
        "S3, Glacier",
        "CloudWatch, EBS volumes",
        "CloudWatch, EFS",
        "S3, EFS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["S3, Glacier"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "567",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "ML Implementation and Operations",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "For advanced queries of your CloudWatch logs, once you have stored your logs on S3 you can use ______ to query and analyze data directly from S3",
      "answers": [
        "Athena",
        "ElasticSearch",
        "SQL",
        "Hadoop"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Athena"]
    }
  }
]